I believe in abundance. So what I would
say to those people is Bitcoin is a
hedge against abundance. If we're
heading to a world of abundance, I think
5% of your portfolio [music] always
deserves to have some insurance policy
just like your house or your car or
anything. So if you want to keep your
wealth, why not put 5% into the asset
that young people believe is a real
asset?
>> You talk about 5%. How much of your
personal portfolio in Bitcoin? I don't
get into
>> Jordy [music] Vissa leading AI macro
nexus research at 22V.
>> A former Weiss CIO and Morgan Stanley
executive a macro strategist
specializing in
>> AI digital assets [music] and economic
transformation. Should someone in his
20s or 30s put all their efforts to buy
a house?
>> I just believe mobility is an option you
always want to have. And I [music] don't
think it's ever been more important than
it is today. I would rather have people
enjoy the ability to be young and travel
when you have the chance rather than
focus on implanting yourself in one
place and buying a house. Do you
consider selling Bitcoin one day?
>> I have no interest whatsoever in selling
those today. The total sum of all the
assets on the planet Earth are about
$750 trillion and crypto is $2.7
trillion. I believe the fiat assets go
down and the crypto assets go higher.
Just so people realize, Ford is still a
company. It's been around for over a
hundred years. If you own the stock,
it's the exact [music] same price as it
was 35 years ago. I'll even say Bitcoin
is the only one I can guarantee will be
higher in 10 years. How about that?
>> What's your answer to someone who says
that a Bitcoin at 60K or 80K or 100K or
120K is expensive in 2026? I missed it.
>> Everyone has their own opinion and most
people that I speak with.
Hey everyone. One of our absolute
favorite things that when shift happens
is to look at our data to improve what
we're doing for you every single week.
And one of the things that we notice
every week when going through our data
is how many of you regularly watch this
podcast but still have not subscribed.
And so if you want to help us get even
better guests every week, take two
seconds and click that subscribe button
just below this video. Thank you for
being with us today and for supporting
us every week. And now let's get to
today's show.
>> Do you like it? What do you like? Tell
me.
>> Huh?
>> Tell us everything.
>> Everything looks good.
>> You asked me questions.
>> Everything looks good. [laughter]
>> Are we happy? Did we have a good
weekend?
>> I had a great weekend. I always have a
great weekend.
>> Yeah. Always. What do you do during the
weekend to have a great weekend? To
disconnect.
>> Uh, breathe, walk through nature, chill
out, eat, cook.
>> What's the What's the nature around
here? Uh, I normally go up to either
upstate New York. I'm going to Maine for
a while. So, I'll be gone for four of
the next five months in Maine. So, I
spend a lot of time up there, a lot of
time out in Utah skiing, and then a lot
of time in Brooklyn.
>> Skiing?
>> Yeah.
>> Wow. Just got skiing a long time ago.
>> No.
>> No. Recent?
>> Uh, in my 40s. Yeah.
>> What What made you want to start skiing
in your 40s?
Risk taker. late risk taker.
>> Um, it was good for my kids, so I wanted
them to have something I didn't have.
And I I had had a taste of it, fell like
a million times, but I'm a type A
person. I went, "Oo, I like this. This
could be good, and I want to do this
when I'm a 100, so let me figure it
out." So, I got my kids skiing when they
could, and then I just took a lot of
lessons with a very high-end group that
taught me how to ski as slow as
possible, which is what I want to do. I
want to be able to ski anything in the
mountain as slow as possible. So,
technical, and I've got a good
engineering mind, and that's why I
wanted to do it. And now I just love it.
But I don't ski like crazy stuff. I just
enjoy nature. Simple.
>> How do you live until 100?
>> How?
>> Yeah, because if you want to ski until
100, you need to live until 100.
>> Well, that's the easy part. The easy
part.
>> Well, you have to stop aging. So, you
have to realize that aging is a disease
and it's not something that has to
happen. So,
>> how deep are you down this rabbit hole?
>> I do a weekly substack on it. So,
[laughter]
I'm fairly uh fairly deep. I have my
aura ring. I have my eyewatch. I can
talk about longevity for a whole
podcast. So,
>> who are you?
>> Who am I?
[sighs and gasps]
I don't know. Just a person who wakes up
every day happy and curious.
>> Tell me a bit more about the longevity
stuff.
[snorts] How did you get how did you get
so fascinated by longevity?
>> I see a problem.
>> I spend time
learning about how I could not have that
problem happen. And it was my
grandfather who died too early in life.
>> And I don't mean when he actually died.
He died probably about the lifespan of
human being in his early 70s, but he
died way before then as far as I was
concerned. He was couldn't walk very
well. He had a huge beer gut. There were
all kinds of things. And I just decided
at that point, what's the solution to
that problem? I want to be able to ski
when I'm 100. Even though at that time
that's not what I was thinking. I was
still fairly young. But I decided at
that point, how do you make sure that
you live a long time? And at that point,
all my research was not on longevity. It
was just on how can I be as healthy as I
can. And then the more that you do that,
if you ever don't do that for a period
of 3 months, you feel really bad. And
you start to realize that the time when
you're the happiest is usually when
you're also the healthiest.
>> What do you not do for 3 months to not
be healthy? Is it not something that I
would say either you're healthy or not?
Like it's something that either you say,
"Okay, I'm going to the gym. I'm eating
clean. This is just like a a habit
actually. I need this thing to feel
better." How can you change that thing?
Well, this is the beauty of um what I
studied and how it came back to heart
rate variability. So, I have this
acronym Minds, which stands for
meditation, immune system, nutrition,
education, sleep.
>> So, what can destroy all of those things
over three months? An injury,
>> um travel, if you're traveling to Asia,
and I would travel extensively at at at
that time of my life. If you've got a
new job and you're
>> flying tomorrow evening to Singapore,
[laughter]
>> there you go. I try to fly as little as
I can to Asia. Now, as you get older,
you have to kind of counterbalance
everything and not travel as much, not
play basketball as much, not all of
these things, not drink as much, not
anything as much. So, I just realized in
that 3-month period that a lot of those
things, I wasn't breathing at the time.
Meditation was not part of my life the
way it is now, but my immune system, I
was getting allergies. And the reason
was I was too run down. I was tired. I
was traveling too much over the poles
back and forth Europe, Brazil, all these
places and work and travel and even
being in relationships with people that
were probably not good. Uh you start
realizing you just got to surround
yourself with joy.
What do you think of u
taking I would not say supplements but
now people talk about peptides there's
bodybuilders or other people or or
sports people who would use some other
type of substances to
perform better. But there's also those
who say if you do it longterm it's not
good. If you have a bad episode to get
back on track, sometimes it can be
really useful to get a kick.
Almost everything that you need from my
studies
>> comes from food. So, usually when you
don't when you need to take a
supplement,
the number one cause is going to be your
diet. So, the first thing that I kind of
focus on because I don't take
supplements. I don't even take Advil.
It's Tylenol, anything, unless I have
to, which I'm going to guess is maybe 10
pills a year. So, how do you get to that
point? How do you not take allergy
pills? How do you not take I just wrote
a Substack on allergy, so that's why
it's kind of front of mind. But, uh,
what do I take supplements for? Well,
the soil's changed in the world, which
means the nutrients in our vegetables
and our animals have gone down no matter
where you get it from. So, you're not
getting as many nutrients as you used
to. How do you get enough magnesium in
your body? Because magnesium is really
important. And as you get older, all of
these things matter because protein
synthesis drops down. So if you want to
stay muscular, if you want to actually
stay young, and muscle is the youth
agent. Well, you can take supplements,
you can take HGH, you can take steroids,
you can take whatever, or you can do
resistance training and have an
inordinate amount of protein.
But then if you don't have enough
vegetables, you're not going to have the
ability of turning that protein or into
muscle because you have to synthesize it
and that takes magnesium and potassium
and calcium and all these things that
come from vegetables. So it's a very
complex system the body and that's why
aging is so easy for it to happen. And
like I said, I go down deep rabbit holes
to try and figure out how I can do it as
naturally as possible. But I'm also a
big believer in artificial intelligence
which will allow us to live forever. So
my goal has been stay as young as I can,
which basically means just stay the same
age as long as you can.
>> So the earlier you fall down the rabbit
hole, the better cuz the
the younger you stay forever.
>> A lot of uh a lot of things go against
you as you get older.
On most trading platforms, crypto lives
in one app, stocks in another, and
commodities such as gold and oil
somewhere completely different.
Variational puts per all of it. Crypto,
equities, commodities, FX, and even
preipo names in one single account with
zero trading fees on every market at any
size. Visit variational.io to see why
variational has quickly become one of
the largest onchain trading platforms.
Big thanks to my friends at Bitwise
Asset Management for backing today's
conversation. Bitwise is a global crypto
asset manager with 11 billion in client
assets and more than 70 crypto
solutions. That includes ETFs, index
funds, SMAs, custom option strategies,
staking, vaults, and more. However you
want to invest in crypto, the experts at
Bitwise have you covered.
What's the first step that someone needs
to take if they
fall down the rabbit hole, the longevity
rabbit hole?
>> First thing they should do.
>> I I really think that people have to
spend a lot of time on nutrition and
understand it. I think nutrition uh is
the key thing for every living creature.
what it uses to convert energy into what
we are. Whether it's a plant that
obviously needs water, needs sun. I
mean, I always found it fascinating as I
went down the longevity
rabbit hole that if you put a plant away
from the sun and you come back later in
the day, it's turned itself to face the
sun because it needs that. So, nutrition
to me is the number one thing for people
and understanding the importance of
balance, diversity. um it'll lead to the
other parts. Your immune system is based
on your microbiome. And to understand
your microbiome, you need to have a
variety of different foods. And you need
to understand what uh it takes to get
it, why fiber is so important in your
diet. You need a certain amount of
fiber. Why do you need the fiber? All of
those things in nutrition will start to
feed back through the body and your
health. And you'll start to realize that
a lot of the problems you have for
longevity uh are directly related to the
food that you're eating. And as time
goes on, the medical community
prescribes pills to to offset those
deficiencies that you've created
yourself. And that's why I think it
should start with nutrition.
The problem with this is
whether you talk about
biohacking or longevity is everyone is
different and if everyone is different,
everyone has different needs because
everyone has different problems.
And this is expensive.
>> Well, let let's go through. Everyone
should um if they have insurance should
be able to get blood work done at least
once a year. And if you have a good
doctor, you can get it done more times.
The blood work is customized to you. Um,
most people don't realize this, but
doctors when you go to visit them, the
most important information the doctor
needs
is how you feel. They ask you, they give
you a hundred questions to fill out. Do
you smoke? Do you drink? How often do
you do that? They need all that
information. You have all that
information. So, if you lie on the
thing, then they have no way of actually
knowing what's going on. The blood work
is a way to give you a sense as to what
your age is. um if you have insurance
and can go get other tests, you can go
get them. But you're right, it is
expensive. And this is one of the
reasons why the distribution of wealth
problem has contributed to
the unhealthy situation that the country
is in. The rise of diabetes, the need
for ozic. All of these things have come
from a combination of nutrition, but
also because we created fast food and we
really drove people towards things. And
then you have all the diet books that
said only eat meat, only eat this, don't
eat meat. All of these things contribute
to a lack of diversity and they create
imbalances for sure.
What's your thoughts on um you talked
about ompic there's these different
peptide things obviously a big trend. We
could probably talk about it for 10 or
15 or 20 hours.
My first thought having not tried any
but having tried when I had really bad
health issues I tried some pro hormones
>> which is 17th of the potency of
testosterone
>> which at crazy effect I realized
everything is biochemistry I sleep super
deep these crazy vivid dreams I don't
pro procrastinate anything I go smash
work I go smash the gym 15 days it's
crazy right 15 days in a row
well it's amazing it's like this
limitless uh movie, right? But there
must be a downside to it. If you're
taking a pill that now there's this
retita true tide thing that people say,
"Oh man, in 3 months these are my
results." I hear some people saying, "I
I fell out of love with my partner
because of these different things like
because they rewire the way your brain
works." I mean, you say you try to do
everything uh
naturally. So, I guess you have some
pretty strong thoughts on these things.
I I do but um so I I I don't know how
much you know or people know about heart
rate variability but um I believe it is
the closest so I'm a I'm a data person.
I like data but I especially like data
that tells a very good story. So any
kind of interesting data point that is
uh kind of breaks the mold of what
you're saying is very important to me.
So heart rate variability
is really a balance indicator. So you
were describing feeling good and being
energetic and all of these type A
qualities
>> that make you look on the outside like
you're super healthy.
But there's a reason why meditation,
there's a reason why nature, there's a
reason why breathing. Uh the word that
always has to come up is balance. Um,
I'm very big into uh little tiny simple
things to say to people. And if everyone
wants to know within 10 years whether
they're going to die or not, a simple
test is to see if you can stand on one
leg for 10 seconds.
And if you go through why balance is so
important, it your brain has to be good.
Your ears like everything up here has to
be good. Your core has to be good. Your
legs, if you've got a beer gut, you're
going down. If you don't have strength
in your body as you get older, you go
down. The number two killer in the world
behind heart disease is falling. And
it's not from dying from the fall. It's
that once you fall and you're older,
muscle atrophy goes much faster than
when you're younger. Uh, and so all of
these things line up. So I I really I
for people um I always think of a leaf
in the wind just kind of floating around
and if the breeze was strong enough, the
leaf wouldn't come down for a long
period of time. And aging is the thing
where you you have more control over
your aging than you realize. And if you
try to get a quick fix for anything,
like you said, there are consequences
and it starts to ruin the balance.
>> Absolutely. I mean, it makes sense.
Obviously
you mentioned uh heart rate variability
as kind of this ultimate KPI.
>> Yes.
>> What is I mean I have that right and I
see that but I actually don't really pay
attention to it.
>> So
>> exactly
>> exactly right. I look more at how much
do I sleep? Do I sleep well? All that
stuff.
>> Uh and and do I train enough and what's
my age on oop right?
>> Yep.
what is heart rate variability and
what's uh considered a healthy heart
rate variability or more. If I'm not
around those numbers,
I should have a kind of a yellow red
flag.
>> So, I'm sure you know what V2 max is.
>> Well, not really.
>> Okay. But, you know, it's another metric
that's important.
>> Yeah. But it's in there, too.
>> It's in there, too. But it is definitely
more for people who are athletic. It's
much more of a how how young is your
heart, how young is the relationship
between your lungs and your heart and
your ability to breathe. So great that
that that one very easy to do. The great
thing about heart rate variability
is number one, you have control over.
So, you mentioned the movie Limitless,
but you didn't mention the documentary
Limitless that was done with Peter Aia
and Chris Hemsworth.
>> And this was on longevity. Um, and they
didn't specifically mention heart rate
variability uh in any kind of manner. I
think they said it once. And the only
reason I know that is because I looked
it up in AI to see because I was writing
about this. And it's an important
documentary for anyone who wants to
start to realize some of the myths
behind this. But also, it starts with a
very simple thing. Chris Hemsworth has
virtual reality goggles on and he's
standing in a room like this.
And as he puts them on, he thinks he's
now on the ledge of a building a 100
stories up.
All they have him all hooked up to his
body and the metrics that are happening.
Everything's freaking out now. He knows
he's standing in a room. So, this is not
a type A thing. This is a It just shows
how much your mind, even though you know
what's going on, it's coming through
your eyes and it's sending a signal to
your body. This is not your brain. You
have no control over this part. So,
heart rate variability is the ability
for you to go into fight or flight, but
then quickly go back to something
normal. This is important for
firefighters. This is important for
policemen. This is important for Navy
Seals who have to stay underwater for a
long period of time. How do you swim
underwater for 3 minutes? How do you do
that? Most people can't make it for 20
seconds before they start freaking out.
So heart rate variability is the
relationship I like to say between our
biological brain, the one that is like a
plant, the one that is like a lion. It
does not have this thing in our head.
And then we have our
computational brain. The one that
separates us from animals that allows us
to think about things. Some of the
things that happen are not created here.
Everything that we do physically to try
and make ourselves healthy, we're
thinking of. The part that we don't do
is the part that our body is sending up.
And to control that, to not overreact to
things is something that is genetic. It
is how you were brought up in the house.
We don't remember anything from zero to
four. That's a long period of time for
us not to remember what happened to us.
There's a lot of things that are brought
into our body that we have to overcome.
And that's why the Buddhist monks and
all the meditation and all of the things
and the cosminauts who were really the
originators of heart rate variability
and why they did it to make sure people
didn't panic in space. It's a very
important metric to see how in line how
aligned you are in your body with the
ability of calming it down and
identifying when you're in a state of
fight or flight.
>> [snorts]
>> What does it look like a number?
>> So your question about an age, the
greatest thing about this metric is if
you look at it and Aura Ring gives it to
you. This is what it looks like with
age. It's directly correlated. So you
can keep your heart rate at the same
level. It kind of varies. If you keep
working out, it'll stay there. Heart
rate variability declines as you get
older. So the so the so the age I see on
my whoop or on your ura biological age
is basically directly linked to this
heart rate variability or
>> I don't know what they have in their
algorithm they don't disclose what goes
in but I guarantee you it is not solely
heart rate variability what you can look
at is for everyone who uses this with
their age what is the average it'll be
and they give you a range so on aura
ring mine when I basically made the
decision that I wanted to as you say
biohack But really what I wanted to do
was commit down the rabbit hole raising
my HRV. That's what my whole substack is
about. And so at the time it was in the
middle of the range for my age. And I
decided, well, let me change some things
in my life to make it go higher. How
what do I have to do to make it go
higher? So according to my blood work,
according to everything that I did, my
physical activity, my ability to do
things with people in their 20s, I was
physically healthy, but my HRV was only
average, and I wanted it to be above
average. I wanted to see if I could make
it go higher. And that took a lot of
different things. So this is somewhat
similar to anyone who wants to kind play
this, but what I realized was for HRV,
it is such a complex thing. If you want
to lose weight, it's easy to figure out
how to lose weight. you just starve
yourself or you change your diet and you
go exercise more to raise your HRV. Very
few people that I've met cuz people
reach out to me have been able to do it.
So that's where I spent my time trying
to figure out how to do it.
How different do you feel when you have
an average HRV for your age versus when
you manage after
a few months or a few years to increase
that number?
The biggest change for me uh is 100% not
ruminating over things, not worrying
about things for very long.
>> Interesting.
>> Um and that leads to more happiness. So
a type A person when they leave that gym
and they're feeling good, I don't care
who it is. I've worked in the industry
long enough to see everyone.
They're stressed when they leave the
gym. They might be full of energy, but
then they go to work. They're not
getting paid enough. they should be
running things. Uh they're not how are
they going to get on that next trip?
Everything is about money and about the
way the world is. So there's no way that
people that go in the gym to kill
themselves and work hard are not caring
about the things in life that cause
stress or cause need and desire and
everything else. So for me, it was
really the ability to not ruminate about
things. And
it just it it's much easier when your
HRV is high.
What's another you mentioned
do doctors multiple times and pills. The
classic thing is doctors give you a pill
to to fight a symptom but not the
underlying cause. And that's when then
you enter into a a rabbit hole of
functional medicine or biohacking or or
or or longevity.
which means that there's a big issue out
there in terms of health and how the
entire system is built which we can
probably talk for another 30 hours.
What's another
industry
where you fell down the rabbit hole? I
mean you've been finance for 30 years,
right?
tell us more about the finance industry
rabbit hole and the actual
truth,
the HRV that you found in the rabbit
hole for finance that actually
is not what people think.
I I I
guess I picked up on this quickly. Um
I moved up the ladder on Wall Street
very quickly. Um
>> in general, meaning I I started at a
firm uh and within five years I was
asked to open an office for the firm
overseas that was just opening in in
Brazil and this was at Morgan Stanley.
So it wasn't a small company, it was a
big company. Um so just on itself that
was not normal. But when you add in the
fact that I gradu graduated from a
college that they don't recruit at for
jobs at a high level, I was hired as
basically a uh a controller and someone
who
did accounting stuff in the derivative
area, but I um my father didn't graduate
high school. So I really I was the first
person to graduate college in my in my
family. So, I was not someone that
really knew anything about the industry,
but I had a good math brain. So, here's
where the rabbit hole was very quickly
for me. I realized after about the first
six months that even though I didn't go
to the best schools in the world,
I knew I was as smart as everyone.
Now, when I say as smart, the things
that go into trading, the things that go
into derivatives, calculating math in
your head, all of those things. I wasn't
trained in school now, but my father
trained me in handicapping a horse race.
So, I realized very early that this myth
that you have to go to the best schools
to actually succeed at something was a
myth. What I also realized there were
two things that happened. One was the
bigger the sociopath risktaker,
the more likely that you make the most
money.
So if 10 people are sociopaths,
psychopaths, whatever you want, and f
and they all take as much risk as
possible, at least one of them will make
lots of money, even if they're cheating,
stealing, doing whatever. And then as
time goes on, people associate smarts
with the big wallet. M
>> so that is a myth. That is a rabbit hole
that I realized very quickly. And then I
also realized that those are some of the
most miserable people I've ever met in
my lifetime. So number one,
money doesn't mean the person's smart.
And number two, money doesn't bring
happiness in every case. Now you want to
have money to enjoy good things in life.
But I started to realize that very
early. And because I didn't come from
any money, I didn't understand this
concept. So I will tell everyone the
metric
for determining a lot of the success
that is money based in Wall Street is
based on zip code. It's based on where
you were born. Um if you're born in the
right zip code, you probably had a lot
of advantages that other people didn't
have. And I recognized this when I moved
to Brazil and I saw people that never
were able to leave the countryside and
be poor their whole lives. And the main
reason was because they grew up in a zip
code that didn't have education. And so
over time, as I've become more involved
with artificial intelligence, as they
become more involved with teaching
people as part of my life, uh, I care
more about kind of breaking this myth
and this arbitrage. People are much
smarter than they realize. They just
need to use their brain, remain curious,
and talk to someone who's smarter than
they are. And that's the beauty of
technology and artificial intelligence.
>> When did you start understanding the
concept of money?
Because you said money doesn't make you
necessarily happy, but people need it.
And people need to understand, everyone
need to understand
>> what money is,
how to make some, how to grow it, how to
keep what you made because it's hard to
make.
So because I grew up with very little
money uh at the very early stages, I was
just grateful to
be getting the money I was getting. And
it was not it was not large uh at the
very beginning because when you start at
the bottom of a firm and they keep
telling you, well, we can only pay you
twice as much in your case as what you
were, which is great percentage-wise,
but you know, if you double a penny
every day, it becomes a big number after
about 30 days, which is fine. Uh but I
realized that even though I didn't need
much money and my initial statement was
if I ever make $100,000 in a year,
I will be happy. Now, my father was a
construction worker. So, this was where
my mentality came from. He's not making
$100,000 in in a year. So, my mentality
was that would be a level that I would
be set for life. And what I realized is
no matter how much money you make, you
always think you need more.
And the second thing is money becomes
the competition.
You I I didn't care about school because
my father didn't graduate. So I wanted
to find the level that I could keep my
parents off my back. So they said, "How
are you doing school?" As long as I was
getting a B+, they were going to leave
me alone. So I was like, "Okay, that's
what I'll get." So, I did the least I
could to get the grades that would keep
them off my bat. I wasn't one of those
kids that just would work hard and hard
and hard. Now, what I cared about was
sports. In sports, whether it's scoring
a basket, scoring a goal, hitting a home
run, doesn't really matter. You have
some benchmark, some KPI, as you said.
Now, when you get to work, it's all
money because you realize titles don't
matter. I was a partner at Morgan
Stanley I think when I turned 30 and I
realized this doesn't actually change
anything in my life getting a title. I
don't care if I'm a president or a
partner or whatever. What I care about
is give me more money then pay me more
money. And as time went on I realized
that money didn't no matter how much you
had it did not make you happy. And more
importantly when you have children as
they start looking around you realize
wait I grew up without money. I worked
hard. You guys have money. Are you going
to work as hard? So, it creates issues
that you don't think about later in
life. [laughter]
Quick shout outs to our legendary
long-term windshift events partners
without whom none of this would be
possible. Thank you to Cast, my go-to
global money app to store, earn, move,
and spend stable coins across 170 plus
countries directly with Apple Pay or a
physical card. On top of that, I can
also get paid in USD and euro with my
cast virtual account. Use my promo code
shift SH if
my link below to get 10% off your
membership. Earn [snorts] up to 3%
instant USD cash back on every card
spend and get up to $250 in cash for
referring your friends. No banks, no
borders, just money that moves with you
with stable cash rewards.
So what's the point of making all this
money if it's to at the end realize I
if I mean happiness comes from probably
like simple things obviously to have
enough money but then even the people in
my life probably don't want to attract a
partner who is not too money
um thirsty and then you have your kids
but actually having more money creates
more problems because they probably
become more entitled. What's the
freaking point of all of this? Yeah, but
there [laughter] there there's no answer
to life in general. If someone said how
do you be happy, there is no formula. So
I think money along with you know the
partners you choose in life um the jobs
you choose uh these are all choices that
people have and as time goes on and you
get older you know the phrase that I use
more than ever if you surround yourself
with only things that bring you joy you
will have a much better life now
>> money
will bring people joy being able to go
experience a trip in Italy or in uh
Japan.
Those are phenomenal things like to see
cultures that are different and not
everyone has the money to do that. And
until virtual reality is perfect and
people can go visit these places and
actually not go anywhere, which I
believe will occur at some point. Uh
money is the thing that allows people to
do things unfortunately they can't. It
allows you to be more secure in your
health if something does go wrong and
you have the money to take care of it.
So all of these things unfortunately the
way the system is right now uh money is
just something that's there and if
people want it it's actually easier
easier than they think to get in today's
world especially with artificial
intelligence. So I have tried to make it
a point right now to help people
both younger than me, older than me, uh
in a variety of different ways, all
using artificial intelligence because it
really does allow you to get that
arbitrage that I said at the beginning,
which is just because you went to a good
school doesn't mean you're smarter than
another person. It just means you
memorize things in school better than
they did
>> or you were taught by people that were
smarter. But the reality is now with
artificial intelligence, you can learn
from the smartest person you would ever
meet in your lifetimes
times two, three, four, 10, 100 and just
growing every day. And I think that just
normalizes the arbitrage that's been
there. [snorts]
>> AI is about to make everything abundant.
Can you explain?
>> Yeah, within the next 15 to 20 years,
um, I think people are going to be blown
away by
how much things are at our fingertips.
Uh it's really hard for me to have
conversations with people about
artificial intelligence these days
because I need to know how much they use
them.
>> Um and for the most part people don't
use them, at least nowhere near as much
as they should. Partly because schools
don't let kids use them.
Workplaces select what you're allowed to
use. They don't allow you to use
everything. They don't want you to put
your data into it. So, it's very hard to
use it all the time, which is why I
don't work for anyone and never will
again because now that I have my own
digital employees, I don't get
complaints and I also don't have to deal
with bosses or anyone that I've ever had
um to kind of tell me what I'm supposed
to do or not do or regulators to tell me
what I can't do. It's my business. I can
do what I want. So, uh, I think when
people start to realize that every year
exponential change is happening quickly
and that aging will no longer be
something you have to worry about, um,
that we will have cures for almost all
diseases in 20 years. Uh, we will have
cures for every problem. And the easiest
way for me me to get people to accept it
is to use something they're all familiar
with. So the movie Oenheimer when it
came out, if you really paid attention
to it and you converted into artificial
intelligence, we had a huge problem in
the world and they wanted to solve it by
coming up with the atomic bomb.
So they took all of the smartest people
and brought them into one location to
figure out how to solve this one
problem.
The IQ of Albert Einstein was estimated
to be 160. The IQ right now of chat GPT
5.5
is above 140. By the end of this year,
we'll have Einsteins everywhere. Which
means we already have AI agents. You
will have billions of Einsteins that can
work on every problem. So, forget
nuclear, forget atomic bombs. Solving
fusion, fision, cancer, name whatever
problem you've ever wanted to solve. We
will have Manhattan projects going on 24
hours a day solving all of the world's
problems. Which means abundance will be
here because behind every cost of
something, behind everything that goes
on is energy and technology. And if
energy is free
>> and we've solved that problem, if we
don't have to worry about where copper
comes from because we've come up with
advanced materials that we can 3D print,
I can do this all day long. It will be
work humanoids working. All of these
things will happen. So we will within 20
years be at a point where abundance is a
real thing.
>> If everything becomes abundant,
does that mean that everything becomes
more affordable?
it should um and I'm sure there'll be
some outliers like going to Mars and
things that are kind of new and people
may want to do uh but for daily living
and for things that are the basic needs
of transportation and food and health
and everything else I see absolutely no
reason why they all won't be free
if we get pretty much everything at low
cost or and free because AI makes
everything abundant.
Why do we still need to build wealth?
This is a good question and um it's
probably the reason that I've I've ended
up in the the crypto
mindset.
Uh I I don't know how to answer it other
than
you have to go back to before
capitalism, which is
a world with communities.
And so this is something I I don't I
don't think people um understand.
This form of countries is like looking
at a map that didn't exist 2,000 years
ago. you kind of did and you had wars
that were going on, but people were
living in little communities and they
were bartering skills. They were not
going to the store and buying things
2,000 years ago. And it was when the
plow basically started that it allowed
people, oh, one thing can feed lots of
people. So, the rest of you people can
now go off to the city and become
doctors and lawyers and all these
different things and start going to
school. And that is what started this
whole job thing. It's what started the
whole you go out you do this where in a
community people were helping each other
out and doing things. There's a reason
why I go to Maine and I always say Maine
is the state in the United States where
capitalism is only peaked its head
inside. It's still a very very laid-back
place. Still has lost men. Still has
people that I can relate to. It's very
calm. It's filled with nature. There's
very few people there. And it's a
beautiful country on the coast or
beautiful state on the coast. There's
just not many places that can compare
for me uh to Maine, but I go there for
that reason because it reminds me or
makes me think about community much
more. And I think that's going to be the
case as time goes on. So the wealth
part, if you don't need money,
human beings are still greedy. They're
still power hungry. They still want
that. And I don't think that's going to
leave because animals have that, too.
They fight over women. They fight over
men. They fight over everything. Animals
are no different on that element. So, I
would imagine that if wealth doesn't
matter, we'll find some way to make sure
it still survives and still show who the
best is in some form. Uh, but I don't I
don't know how to answer it.
How do you get so fascinated by the word
of Bitcoin?
My fascination with it um was from
was looking at it through a window
uh until 2020 until 2020. So before that
I didn't care about it. Um I didn't care
to partake. I I was definitely one of
those people that
understood that the blockchain was
something real and that Bitcoin to some
degree was the way to play the
blockchain.
Uh but I didn't understand it until
2020. And the reason I say 2020, two
things happened in 2020. First was COVID
happened and uh I saw what the
government did which I was already an
exponential innovation a believer in
exponential innovation completely ending
recessions.
Uh and so when COVID happened I saw the
money printing and I listened to human
beings thinking that we'd have a
recession or a depression. And I just
remember having conversations with
people that run major companies who I've
known for a long time
saying the world was going to end. And I
went, "How how can you believe that?
Like we just print enough money and
everything's fine."
And he said, "This is you can't stop
this." And I went, "No, you you can. If
you give people money, trust me, you're
you're you're misrepresenting the Great
Depression. They didn't have money, so
they couldn't get food. But if you just
throw money out of a window to every
single person and you let them order
things on their phone to be delivered,
the world will absolutely be back. And I
couldn't convince them. So I said, "All
right, let me ask it a different way. So
far, we've printed $6 trillion.
If we did a hundred trillion,
would you change your mind?" And there
was always dead silence on the phone.
And that's when I realized at this point
that oh my gosh,
human beings that are even highly
educated believe in this, they believe
in this thing that doesn't exist
anymore,
>> which is
>> recessions
>> and this thing of human emotions
carrying things out. And so knowing that
the distribution of wealth problem was
so big and knowing that the reason we
were printing all this money was for the
people who could not live, that's what
the Great Depression was about. But on
the flip side, all of the wealthiest
people that I were talking to didn't
think there was enough money that could
print that would protect them. So the
wealthy were worried and the poor were
getting their checks and yoloing it. So
I realized there was something strange
that was happening. And so Bitcoin
became more interesting to me because it
started to rally before all of the other
inflation things rallied. And that's
when I realized that whether it was
demographics or whether it was the
distribution of wealth, the masses were
not worried about COVID the same way
that a wealthy person perched behind
their walls with their guards was
worried. Then the next year, my son
turned $700 into $70,000 and then
subsequently lost it all when the winter
of crypto came. But in that time where I
said to him, "Hey, you're 13. I've got a
bunch of portfolio managers that work
for me. I'm I want you to come in like
you're a portfolio manager. I want me to
explain your positions and how you've
made this money. And we went on a ski
trip. And he talked to me about it. And
it was phenomenal. He knew every token.
He knew why he was invested in them.
Some of them are still around today. Um
and it made me realize that there was
something here that was interesting to
him. And when I asked him how he learned
all of this, it was through Reddit and
through Twitter. And that's when the
phrase pump and dump was brought to my
occasion. That's when all of these
things and I went, "So this is a real
thing. Like this is something my kid
turned into real money. He knows about
it. It's no different than the game that
I play. It's ideas
>> that are hopefully going to be
monetized. that's no different than
Apple or all these things that I'm
involved in. So I listened to Michael
Sailor about seven times over the course
of the next week. And luckily, Michael
was the only spokesperson really at that
time that was getting attention. The
reason I say luckily is because I said I
was already a believer in exponential
innovation. The reason that's critical
to this journey and for anyone who's
hearing this that has not yet entered
the Bitcoin belief system, what Michael
Sailor talked about, which very seldom
gets amplified,
is his business was destroyed
by exponential innovation. His business
was destroyed by Microsoft and then the
government came in to print a bunch of
money and his business was now going to
get destroyed again by the government.
And the reason that was important is
because they were moving rates to zero.
He already had a dying business where it
was bleeding every year, but he had tons
of money on the balance sheet. So it's
not that he didn't make a lot of money
and now the government was in his mind
stealing from him. And so he went back
as a smart guy who graduated from MIT.
He's not a dummy. And he went to go
learn about the history of money. Now
these are things that I was already
familiar with. So when he spoke about
those things, I already got that. He was
talking to me about how the future is
about all companies being disrupted. And
that's what I saw. AI will destroy all
businesses. Every single business will
have a shorter lifespan than it used to
have. All of them. Even the ones that
are going parabolic right now. And so
for me, that was my understanding of the
distribution of wealth problem is that
the game will speed up. It will go much
faster. The volatility of Bitcoin, which
is no longer the same as what it was
back then, will decline over time. And
we will see it in my world. The world of
Micron technology and the world of
Nvidia and the world of all these places
where now those volatilities are at the
same level as Bitcoin's old volatility.
>> But no one is complaining about those
because they're making money off those
and that they call it a bubble. So
Bitcoin joined my life back in 2020 and
2021.
What's your thesis on Bitcoin explained
as simply as possible
to a 40 or 50 or 60 year old person who
doesn't really understand it?
>> So the first thing I say to those people
is do you really understand what the
fractional reserve banking system is?
And if you do, please explain it because
you don't know what it is.
>> Go back to It's a Wonderful Life the
movie. I don't know if you've seen it,
Kevin. It's a Wonderful Life. There's a
scene in it. It's the mo, you know, one
of the most popular movies of all time
and it's played every year at Christmas.
But there's a scene in there where
there's a run on a bank. This is taking
place during the Great Depression. And
at some point with all the people in
there, they go, "Your money's not here.
Your money's in their house." And they
he describes the fractional reserve
banking system. You give us your money
and then we lever it up and lend it out
to everyone else in the community. And
as long as everyone doesn't try to get
their money back at the same time,
everything is fine. So for people who
say they don't understand Bitcoin, the
first thing I say is, do you actually
understand the system you're playing in
as it is right now? The second thing is
there are only three modes in my
lifetime that I believe
religion has lasted for thousands of
years. Gold has lasted for thousands of
years. Bitcoin has been chosen by
hundreds of millions of people around
the world since the white paper came out
as a place of a store of value. The
store of values that people invest in
today, their house, bonds, private
equity, private credit, stocks, I don't
care what it is, they have a belief
system in those and they believe there's
a mathematical side to it. So, as long
as the math is real, it's fine. So, what
I what we talked about before, I believe
in abundance. So what I would say to
those people is Bitcoin is a hedge
against abundance.
>> If we're heading to a world of
abundance,
I think 5% of your portfolio of your
wealth that you've accumulated over time
always deserves to have some insurance
policy just like your house or your car
or anything. So, if you want to keep
your wealth, why not put 5% into the
asset that young people believe is a
real asset? And they're getting more
money every day handed down from people
who are taking OMIC and not surviving
long enough to actually live their life
that they want to live. So, let's take
some of that money. So, Bitcoin is a
hedge against abundance.
>> You talk about 5%. How much of your
personal portfolio in Bitcoin?
>> I don't get into what it's the it's the
largest percentage of my net worth at
this point. Now again, anyone who
invests in Bitcoin from [snorts] 2020
on, it's almost impossible not to
because you're talking about something
that's up over 10 times even with the
level it is today. So for everyone
listening, I've never sold any of it. So
the way that you accumulate wealth like
Warren Buffett is if you believe in
something and it was a small percentage
of your portfolio at the beginning and
then it does so well, it becomes the
largest portion. So,
>> do you consider selling Bitcoin one day?
>> Maybe. I I I have no interest whatsoever
in selling it as of today. I don't even
think it's gotten anywhere near where
it's going to get. And just so people
know the valuation of it, the total sum
of all the assets on the planet Earth
are about $750 trillion and crypto is
2.7 trillion. M
>> I believe in abundance the fiat assets
go down and the crypto assets go higher.
Bitcoin is the only beneficiary of the
crypto assets that I know for a fact
will be here 10 years from now.
>> No offense to all the people out there
who like all these other things, but I'm
it's the only one I'm sure of
>> will be here in 10 years. The there will
be plenty that do better than Bitcoin
over the next 10 years, but it's the
only one I can say with certainty will
still be here. And just so people
realize, Ford is still a company. It's
been around for over a hundred years. If
you own the stock, it's the exact same
price as it was 35 years ago. So, I'll
even say Bitcoin is the only one I can
guarantee will be higher in 10 years.
How about that? So,
quick shout out to the legendary team at
Jupiter, the DeFi super app. Anything
you want to do on chain, from trading to
earning yield, you can just use Jupiter.
Personally, I'd recommend getting the
Jupyter wallet on either your phone or
your laptop. 10 times faster and 10
times cheaper than the competition.
You're going to love it. Thank you to
the awesome team at Athena for backing
today's conversation. Athena is one of
the fastest growing projects in DeFi
with over $7 billion in stable coin
supply and an average 11% APY on SUSD
and importantly, zero DPEGs since
launch, which is exactly what you want
from a stable coin. Go check them out by
following the link in the description
down below.
How big do you think this Bitcoin thing
gets?
If we have infinite money printing and
infinite abundance thanks to AI,
I I think it's hard to say because the
true value of Bitcoin in the sense of
what it's replacing has to do with how
much AI causes deflation. M
>> so if everything is free then money is
not important that Bitcoin
doesn't need to be any higher than it is
today. It it it's part of the thing that
I don't think people understand is it's
all about purchasing power of things. If
everything is free then why does the
value of Bitcoin matter just like the
other things don't matter. So, I haven't
thought about it other than as a hedge
against the other wealth that's been
there because what should happen up
until abundance is Bitcoin should
outperform every asset on the planet.
Everything. Not a maybe a company for a
year, but over the course of every five
years, you should look back and be like,
what was the best performing asset? That
was Bitcoin. And that's what's happened
since its beginning. And that's the way
I believe it is that it should just
outperform everything over time. This is
not about to stop happening.
>> Not in my mind.
>> What's your answer to someone who says
that a bitcoin at 60k or 80k or 100k or
120k is expensive or is too expensive
today in 2026. I missed it.
>> Again, everyone has their own opinion
and most people that I speak with since
I'm in most of the people I speak with,
it's funny. I I I spend one leg in the
crypto world, one leg in the Tradfi
world. Uh the video I do every week on
YouTube is 80%
90% Trafi. I'm about to start a second
one which will be 90% crypto. Um and the
reason is because I believe at the end
of this year that those people who don't
believe there's any value to it are
starting to change their mind. Uh and
that's because of tokenization. That's
because of stable coins. uh circle kind
of got them going last year. There's a
communication that's happening in the
equity market that ends up in Bitcoin,
Bitcoin miners, the AI compute story.
They're the worlds are
they're merging. So for anyone who who
thinks the value is wrong, I will just
tell you that I look at it relative to
the two worlds. There's the digital
economy which owns our world right now
with the internet and with social
platforms and the mag seven. And then
there's the money side, the digital
money side, which is still very, very
small relative to the other side. So, I
think it's going to go up significantly
from here.
>> You mentioned 90% crypto in your future
videos. You didn't say 90% Bitcoin.
>> You mentioned crypto.
>> There's a reason for that.
>> Why?
>> My view on um Bitcoin is not the way
most people have been trained to think.
So, Bitcoin is the S&P 500.
>> Mhm.
>> It's amorphous. It is the thing that
survives over time. The S&P 500 could
have 500 new companies next year and
people would still be invested in it.
>> Bitcoin is the end result of all of
these tokens coming and going and coming
and going. The excess wealth that's
created goes into Bitcoin and then we go
fund another vehicle. So, Bitcoin to me
is the thing that'll be here. So when I
say 90% crypto, the audience cares about
things other than Bitcoin. I myself care
more about Bitcoin, but I'm a macro
person. I also care more about the S&P
than I do about individual stocks.
>> Does that mean that you have or could
one day invest in another crypto asset
than Bitcoin?
>> I own Ethereum right now.
>> Um and again, I I believe Ethereum will
outperform Bitcoin this year. And this
is all in the network effects. I believe
people are not fully understanding the
importance of tokenization.
I don't think they've fully understood
the importance of stable coins for
Ethereum and tokenization for Ethereum.
And that just leads me to believe that
by the end of this year, because
Ethereum is the easiest asset in my
opinion with inside the crypto world to
be converted into a stock that people
are familiar with, a discounted cash
flow yield, all of that stuff. I just
think Ethereum is is is probably going
to outperform Bitcoin. And maybe Salana
outperforms Ethereum, maybe Sooie
outperform. I I I don't know. I'm
focused and Ethereum is the only other
one I own at this point.
What are some other scarce assets that
you are invested in
>> that are not Bitcoin related?
>> Well, so currently there's a lot of
scarce assets that I'm invested in. Um,
>> DRAMM, so memory, uh, optical fiber,
optical semiconductors, power
semiconductors, those are all scarce,
>> but let's make it easier for people not
on just on the stock side. Um, just this
week I rotated out of most of my memory
stocks and into silver. So I own silver,
I own gold, um, I own copper, I own
countries that mine those things. I own
stocks that mine those things. So I'm a
very big believer in scarce assets. So
my videos are all focused on being long
scarcity and short abundance. I don't
believe in owning any software companies
uh, that are SAS related. I think they
will be disrupted by AI. I don't know
any of the hyperscalers at this point.
I'm fully focused on the companies that
make assets that people can't get right
now that are in shortage. They won't be
in shortage forever,
>> but they will be for the next few years.
>> What about real estate?
>> Should someone in his or her 20s or 30s,
you have kids.
>> Mhm. Should someone in his or 20s or 30s
put all their efforts into working hard
to buy a house which our parents would
be so proud of?
Um I
would be extremely happy if my kids
would never um own a home. Um, I am
definitely uh my my oldest daughter has
called me the world's oldest millennial
because of things like this. Um, I just
believe mobility is an option you always
want to have.
>> And um, I don't think it's ever been
more important than it is today. And I
just mean that from the basis of
you don't know what you're going to
think about. You might visit a city and
be like, "Oh my gosh, it's nice here."
as you travel more, you want to have the
options to do that. And work can be done
really anywhere. And with artificial
intelligence, I mean, I I spend my goal
is to spend a third, a third, a third
broken up between Maine, Utah, and
Brooklyn, New York.
I think everyone should have that kind
of ability to do that. And you can
because there's lots of people that I
see living in that have moved to Europe.
They live in a different country like
every six months. and they just move
from Montenegro to to to France and then
back over. It's I see this all the time
on X. So, I I would rather have people
enjoy the cha the the ability to be
young and travel when you have the
chance rather than focus on, you know,
planting yourself in one place and
buying a house.
>> And it's not because you want to live in
three different places in the year that
you need to own a house or a flat in all
these places, right? It's kind of back
to what you said in the beginning
regarding
this kind of like status game or money,
right? It feels today that the home is
more of a status game than actually a
smart investment.
So, a phrase that I said to someone who
asked me for wisdom on how to stay
young, the first thing that came out of
my mouth was do new. And the reason
that's important, if you go to the same
restaurant every week, if you take the
same commute in every week, if you if
you have a routine oriented job, your
brain is aging very very quickly. When
you do something new, it actually makes
your brain younger.
>> So I believe if you live in a place for
too long and you take the same thing in,
and this is another thing I saw from my
grandfather. I just saw him aging and he
did the same thing every day. He had the
same food in the morning, the same food
at lunchtime, something different at
dinner, but it was one of five things
that happened during the week. And he'd
sit down, have his cookies, he'd put his
feet up, he'd watch all on like
clockwork. That's not a good way to go
through life. There has to be
variability. Things thrive when you
stress them more. And our body shows
that with workouts. You seem like you
work out, okay? If you do the same
workout every day, it'll start having
less impact on your body. You have to
vary things up.
>> This still goes against building
companies, for example, or building
a physique or I mean, you need to do
things with a certain routine to
actually become better at those things.
>> Well, when you say a routine, um,
habits. Well, so I have a smoothie every
day,
>> but inside that smoothie, the
ingredients
change. I mean, I I have
over a hundred plants in my smoothie,
over 100. And a lot of its powders. Um,
it's it's dehydrated stuff, but it's a
way for me to get a ton of antioxidants
and a ton of things to make sure that I
meet my daily needs. Um, so I don't view
that as as necessarily routine, but I
vary up things. Workouts, too. I do
three to four different types of
workouts during the week. I never do the
same, you know, routine. I use different
people and I make sure I go to classes
that are different. I do different
things on the bike. I I I vary things
up. So, I think you're mistaken if you
believe you have to do the same routine.
I think where routines become important
is to make sure that you don't forget
things and that they're incorporated
into getting them done.
>> So I do breathe every day when I every
day unless I have some a trip or
something. But when I wake up in the
morning,
>> the first thing I do, first thing chop
some garlic, go sit on the couch and I
meditate for 15 to 20 minutes. Then I go
take the garlic and I go have a tonic
with a bunch of things in it for the
first thing of the day. Those two things
are routine for me every single day that
I can do them. But part of that is
because I believe it is critical for my
health and I need to shove it in every
day. But it's not something I would view
as as a OCD routine oriented thing where
I could be doing something new at 5:00
in the morning instead.
>> Thank you so much, Jordy, for doing
this. We probably covered like 5% of the
topics I thought we'd cover, but it was
amazing.
uh and means that we might have another
one in the future. That was awesome.
Thank you.
>> It was great. And very seldom do podcast
start with me on longevity. So felt
good.
>> Interesting.
>> And you could have gone lots of places.
I got a lot of things in my head to talk
about. So,
>> well, we'll do a part two and we'll talk
about a bunch of other things.
>> Great. Sounds good.
>> Nice. Nice. Well, I go like if you start
talk about longevity, which I think is
super interesting, obviously we're going
to have to talk about that. Well, you
care about it clearly. So,
>> yeah. I mean, I just care. Yeah. I'm
curious. And uh
>> Yeah. No, but longevity
>> the HRV thing. I just have it, but I I
never look at it. It's true.
>> Yeah. And you should go look and see
what the uh how your age matches up with
it and then realize that there are ways
to raise it. And literally, I write a
Substack every week and it's on one,
this one was on seasonal allergies this
week. And this is because a person who
reads it sent me something saying, "Hey,
have you ever looked at HRV and seasonal
allergies?" I'm like, "Yes, allergies
are not real. Like, allergies are not a
thing." And the person said, "What do
you mean?" And I went, "A peanut allergy
is real." Meaning your body, you could
die from it.
>> Allergies to pollen are not real. They
are your immune system overreacting to a
toxin that enters your body,
>> which [clears throat] means your immune
system is screwed up. So if you want
your immune system to be better,
you should start realizing what
allergies are. It's really just that
your body's o your immune system is
overreacting. That's why when COVID
happened and I remember I was talking to
my mother and I'm like my you have to
understand people are dying from their
immune system overreacting. The virus is
gone before they die.
>> They don't have the virus when they die.
The virus is gone. It's the symptoms
that stay. So the allergy or the virus
it means you have poor health or not
health that is good enough to fight
external thing.
>> Yeah. And it's it's not so HRV measures
balance. Your immune system everyone
your bo a pollen comes in your nose and
your body goes whoa what is that? Mine
does too. I just don't sneeze and cough
and have watery eyes and all that stuff
because my body looks at it. It starts
to fight it and it goes h that's fine.
Let's go back. So I call it your immune
system is drunk. It just doesn't know
what to do. And the reason it doesn't
know what to do is because you haven't
given it all the nutrients to make it
healthy. Your body gets destroyed by
toxins. And that's what I studied to go.
So really it's the soil. Your gut, your
immune system is the soil and it's most
of it's in your gut. So that is the
reason why like if you have allergies,
you want to understand why you have
them. And if you go to the doctor, they
prick you and then they go, "Okay, you
need to take this shot every year and
they just mess with people."
>> It's actually horrendous because they're
trying to get you to survive on clarity
and everything else. So,
>> as you probably know by now, I host some
of the biggest name in Bitcoin and
crypto on my podcast, but a lot of the
best stuff never makes it on air. The
Shift newsletter is where I share that
raw behindthe-scene alpha, the insights,
stories, and lessons straight from my
guests that you won't hear anywhere
else. If you want the real inside take
on Bitcoin and crypto, join my
newsletter, The Shift, in the
description down below.
[music]